

CONTACT



+2348081368649



enopeteroqua@gmail.com



www.benevox.social



Ado-Ekiti, Ekiti State, Nigeria

SKILLS

- Brand oversight
- ProjectManagement
- Data Analysis
- Business
 Development
- Linux expertise
- Unix and Linuxbased tools
- Cloud Solutions
 Architect

PETER ENO

SOFTWARE, DEV OPS ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

Recent graduate looking for an opportunity in software development. Highly poised and dedicated with a strong education in design principles and programming languages. Committed professional offering more than 6 years of experience in the field of web application development. Excellent communication skills and a consistent team player in all sorts of environments. Seeking to expand talents by bringing a wealth of expertise to a well-established company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2018 - Present Freelance Developer

- Created innovative websites with animations, and audio, and video displays.
- Developed graphics for site pages following branding guidelines and best practices.
- Completed website backup and disaster recovery planning daily, reducing data hack or loss risks.
- Integrated advanced UI principles for user-centered design.
- Delivered clean, error-free code matching project scope and minimizing performance issues.

Oct 2019 - Jan 2021

Website Administrator at InvestAfricamedia LTD

- Ensured web server systems ran smoothly and efficiently through periodic test runs and evaluations.
- Conducted in-depth fault finding into website malfunctions to identify problems, make action plans and implement intelligent solutions.
- Created advanced websites, holding up to multiple web pages with web builders including WordPress and React.
- Analyzed website and web server performance, making recommendations for enhancement based on inefficiencies and faults.

SOFTWARE LANGUAGES

javascript		
Python		
React		
SQL		

PETER ENO

DEV OPS ENGINEER

2019 - 2020

Community Manager at Google DSC AJU

- Autonomously implemented social media and communication campaigns in line with agreed GDSC marketing strategies.
- Provided engaging text, image, and video content for my university's Developer Student Clubs social media accounts.
- Recruited, trained, and managed remote teams of dedicated volunteers for university-wide activities.

EDUCATION

2021

Bachelor of Science | BSc. Computer Science Arthur Jarvis University, Cross-River State Nigeria

CERTIFICATIONS

- Coursera Web Developer Certification
- Associate Cloud Engineer
- Udacity Machine Learning Foundations

LANGUAGES

English, French: First Language